“创始吸血鬼”前情提要
KLAUS:
Previously on The Originals.
如果我们不能联手合作
那还有什么意义？
HAYLEY: If we can't create some sort
of community, then what's the point?
不如杀掉彼此早点了事
Kill each other
and get it all over with.
大家寄望我来保护城里人类的安全
I'm invested in protecting
the people of this city,
要做到的话，我需要那把钥匙
and to do that, I need the key.
- 我叫小约帮我偷来的
- 从我叔叔身上
-I had Josh lift it for me.
-Off my uncle.
我哥哥15年前教过我这个密码
My brother taught me this code
15 years ago.
- 你是克劳斯的父亲
- 我需要你
-You're Klaus' father?
-I need you.
- 我能做什么？
- 你能让我复活
-What can I do?
-You can bring me back to life.
月光戒指保护狼人免受诅咒之苦
A moonlight ring to protect
werewolves from the curse.
- 你想要我怎么做？
- 我想知道它放在哪个石头里
What do I have to do?
I need to know what stone it housed.
一枚带有魔力的戒指
可以阻止这个诅咒的戒指
A ring of empowerment,
something to control this curse.
- 什么样的咒语能够…
- 我母亲的咒语可以
-What kind of spell--
-A spell of my mother's.
我只要求孩子安全
All I ask is that the child
is kept safe.
我们的女儿应该由父母共同养大
在自己的家成长
KLAUS: Our daughter should be raised
by her parents in our family home.
祖先们要我们杀了克劳斯的孩子
The ancestors want us
to kill Klaus' child.
不管你和狼人在密谋着什么
Whatever it is
you got coming with the wolves,
你要知道，我会为了我的人奋战
just know that I'm gonna fight
for my guys,
我会为了我的城市奋战
我会一直奋战到最后一刻
I'm gonna fight for my city,
and I will fight until I am dead.
我想你也会这么做的
I would expect nothing less.
这一袋石头可让我们跑得够远了
Lot of driving for a bag of rocks.
我们天亮前就能到法语区
We'll be in the Quarter by dawn.
你确定那个混合种会遵守他的诺言吗？
You sure the hybrid
will do his part?
海莉会确保他这么做的
Hayley will make sure of that.
是啊，我差点忘了
你未婚妻正将他掌控在股掌之间
Yeah. I forgot your fiancee
has got him around her finger.
知道吗，奥利，我一直待你如亲兄弟
You know, Ollie,
I love you like a brother
但如果你再这么对海莉
别怪我对你不客气
but if you don't lay off Hayley,
we're gonna have a problem.
注意点，罗密欧
Pay attention, Romeo.
好吧，别紧张
我们什么都没做
All right. Relax.
We ain't done anything.
晚安，警言
Evening, officers.
你们两个下车
Step out of the car, both of you.
有什么问题吗？
What's this about?
我想你们最好照他的话做
I think you should do
what the man says.
不然后果可能会很严重
Before things take a nasty turn.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：纽奥良之战
(POLlCE RADlO CHATTER
CONTlNUES)
主演：约瑟夫摩根
我有说过你很棒吗？
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
Have I told you that you're awesome?
你太棒了，就跟阳光
日光戒指
Because you are,
along with the sun, daylight rings.
还有那个穿着背心慢跑的家伙一样棒
That guy jogging in the tank top.
小约，既然你已经得到戒指
我想你该离开了
-Josh.
-Hmm?
Now that you have a ring,
I think you need to leave town.
等等
主演：菲比托金
Whoa, wait.
Are we breaking up?
- 我们要分手吗？
- 我是认真的
I'm serious.
我知道，你向来都很严肃
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
Yeah, I know. Serious is kind of
your default setting,
所以你才需要我在你身边
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
which is why you need me around
逗你开心
to lighten you up.
所以，我是不会走的
主演：莉雅派普斯
Ergo, not leaving.
嘿，你还好吗？
-Hey. You okay?
只是些女巫的事情罢了
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
-Just witch stuff.
马赛尔昨天来找过我
Marcel came to me yesterday.
他想要我施一个隐身咒
He wanted a cloaking spell.
他准备对付克劳斯了，大行动
He's gonna make a move
against Klaus, a big move.
好吧，看来他忘了叫我，真过分
Wow. Okay.
Guess he forgot to call me. Rude.
那你帮他了吗？
Did you help him?
是的，因为我不希望他死
Yes, because I don't want him
to get killed
- 但如果克劳斯发现了…
- 听着
-but if Klaus finds out--
-Hey, look.
如果马赛尔已经有了计划
也许克劳斯会有所觉悟
If Marcel has got a plan,
maybe Klaus will buy a clue,
意识到他不是那么受人欢迎
realize he's a negative
on the popularity chart
然后去过吸血鬼的退休生活
and go into vampire retirement.
我听说棕榈泉是个好地方
I hear Palm Springs is nice.
克劳斯不是我们唯一要担心的
Klaus isn't the only thing
we need to be afraid of.
听着，如果战争来临
Look. If there's a war coming,
答应我你会尽快离开，绝不牵涉其中
promise me you'll go
before you get caught up in it.
你母亲的咒语十分优雅，却也非常复杂
Your mother's spell
is as complicated as it is elegant.
显然她是个极有天赋的女巫
She was clearly a very gifted witch.
是不是这一段？
-ls this the bit here?
我说过了，这很复杂
制片：克里斯多福贺利尔
-Hey, like I said, it's complicated.
她将保护魔法绑定在黑色蓝晶石上
制片：兰斯安德森
She bound protection magic
to black kyanite stones.
拥有石头的狼人
可以不用在月圆时变身
A werewolf with the stones is free
from turning on a full moon.
它还有什么好处吗？
And what of the improvements?
这个咒语能增强速度、力量和敏捷度
This spell will enhance speed,
strength and agility.
这里面应该会提到尖牙
There should be something in there
about fangs.
她当时就是用这个
将我们变成吸血鬼的
It's what my mother used on us
when she turned us into vampires.
不只是尖牙
Not just fangs.
你说过你想保留毒液
You said you want venom
让狼人的咬伤仍然对吸血鬼致命
制片：邦妮怀斯
so the bite is still lethal
to vampires.
就是这里
这会是个好礼物的
Here.
Should make a nice gift.
- 我想海莉一定会十分惊喜
- 不只是给海莉的
-I'm sure Hayley will be thrilled.
-Oh, not just Hayley.
你要帮我做更多
You'll be making
quite a few of these.
不如就一百个吧
Let's call it an even hundred.
这不是我和以利亚的约定
That's not the deal
I made with Elijah.
你现在要打交道的人是我
Well, you're dealing with me now.
而我会给你更多的报酬
And I am offering considerably more.
你以为我们上了床
我就要对你言听计从吗？
You think because I sleep with you,
I'm suddenly at your beck and call.
正因为我们上了床，亲爱的
Because you sleep with me, love,
我才会保护你不受别人的伤害
编剧：查理察尔邦尼，麦克纳度奇
I will protect you from those
who might do you harm,
包括我哥哥
including my brother.
而且，因为我需要你
导演：杰弗利亨特
Because I need you, however,
所以除了我的保护之外
我会给你一样
I'm prepared to offer
something more valuable
更有价值的东西
than my protection.
那是什么？
Which is what?
我母亲的魔法书
这些咒语的出处
My mother's grimoire,
from which I took these spells.
要知道，以利亚只许你窥探其中一二
You see, Elijah is offering you
a mere peek at its pages,
但我会将它完整地双手奉上
but I will grant it to you as a gift
如果你宣誓效忠于我
if you pledge your loyalty to me,
从这些戒指的制造方法开始
beginning with the creation
of those rings.
这就是你一直以来的计划
This has been your plan all along.
你想建立一支狼人军队
而你在利用我来达成这个目的
You want to build a werewolf army
and you're using me to do it.
亲爱的，我不是你的敌人
那些狼人也不是
Sweetheart, I'm not the enemy.
Nor are the wolves.
你那残酷的族人希望你牺牲自己
Your abusive coven expects you
to sacrifice yourself
来复活最后一名收获祭女孩
for the last of the harvest girls.
如果你帮我这个忙
Do this one favor for me
你就再也不用惧怕任何人了
and you need never fear
anyone ever again.
各位，你们该离开了
MAN:
Folks, you need to leave now.
嘿
你这是在干什么？
Hey. Hey, what are you--
我已经试着友善了
I tried to be nice about this.
你以为你是谁？
Who the hell do you think you are?
我是这家秋基汤店的新老板
I am the new owner
of this gumbo shack.
这是刚刚才达成的交易
但我可以告诉你，售价很便宜
Ink is not dry on the contract yet,
but I can tell you, I got it cheap.
自从苏菲德弗罗死后
Business is not what is used to be
这里的生意就一落千丈
since Sophie Deveraux
kicked the bucket.
听着，我不想惹麻烦
Look.
I don't want any trouble.
我不在乎你想要什么
我们来聊聊我想要什么
I don't really care what you want.
Let's talk about what I want.
是的，我叔叔的钥匙
-Right. My uncle's key.
-Hmm.
你说你要用它来
You said you were gonna use it
保护这个城市的无辜人们
to protect the innocents
of the city.
但以你的职业来说，这还真讽刺啊
Seems pretty ironic,
given your line of work.
我是个奉公守法的商人
I'm a legitimate businesswoman
从来没有犯过罪
who's never been convicted
of a crime
同时，身为人类决策群的领袖
and, as leader of the human faction,
钥匙应该是我的
that key is mine.
我给了你时间哀悼
现在时间到了
I gave you time to mourn.
Now time is up.
知道了
Message received.
那就来找找我没有的那把钥匙吧
Let me just go find that key
I don't have.
我的家族在纽奥良生活很久了，卡蜜
My family has been in New Orleans
for a long time, Cami,
比你的家族还久
even longer than yours.
而我们都知道没有朋友
And we've learned
it's a very hard city to get by in
在这个城市很难生存
if you don't have any friends.
我很愿意成为你的朋友
I'd like to be your friend.
所以我给你的期限是明天
So I'm gonna give you
until tomorrow,
在那之后，我就不会这么客气了
and after that,
I won't be so friendly.
放过他
Leave him alone.
我们可以放过他
只要你告诉我们克劳斯的计划
We'll leave your boy alone when
you tell us what Klaus is up to.
我怎么会知道他的计划？
How the hell should I know
what he is up to?
因为我知道你们有碰过面
See, I know you've been meeting him.
你袋子里的那些石头是黑蓝晶石
The stones in your duffel bag,
it's black kyanite.
很稀有
It's pretty rare.
我也了解不少巫术的事
I also know enough about witchcraft
能够分辨哪些是施咒材料
to recognize the ingredients
of a spell.
你要让我再问一遍吗？
So, you'll make me ask again?
好吧
Okay.
你想知道有两个狼人
作为人质的问题所在吗？
You wanna know the problem
with having two werewolf hostages?
那就是你只需要一个
You really only need one.
你们这些新月小子
你们自以为很厉害
You Crescent boys,
you think you're a bunch of badasses
但在1925年
but back in '25,
我消灭了整个葛雷拉家族
I wiped out a whole bloodline
of Guerrera werewolves.
他们可比你们厉害多了
They were a lot tougher than you.
等一下
Wait!
你放了他
You let him go,
我就告诉你石头的事
还有克劳斯
I will tell you about the stones,
about Klaus...
任何事情
whatever.
好吧，好吧
就这么说定了
All right. All right.
A deal is a deal,
但因为这个家伙
在八小时后就要变成狼了
but since Nirvana here is gonna turn
into a wolf in about eight hours,
小迪，把他扔在河口
D, drop his ass off way out
in the bayou.
那我能不能杀了这个蠢货？
Will I at least get to kill this fool?
不，我有个更好的主意
No. I got a better idea.
喂，老哥，什么事？
Yes, brother?
What is it?
看来我们的狼人迷路了，弟弟
It appears our wolves
have gone astray, brother.
- 他们几个小时前就该回来了
- 我们需要找到他们
-They should've been back hours ago.
-We need to find them.
这可能有点困难
Well, that might be a bit tricky.
因为我们在一条偏僻的乡村小路上
You see, we've located their car
on a backroad
发现了他们的车
in the middle of nowhere.
我怀疑他们被人劫持了
I suspect they've been shanghaied.
而你觉得这种讯息不需要告诉我们吗？
And you didn't feel the need
to share this information?
我本打算等我找到了解决方法后
It was my intention to present you
with the problem
才把问题告诉你
only after I'd found
an appropriate solution.
- 那就给我们个惊喜吧
- 说话这时我就要成功了
-Well, do enlighten us.
-I'm closing in on it as we speak.
唯一有胆子抓走我狼人盟友的人
The only person
who would be bold enough
正是最输不起的人
to snatch my wolf allies
is the one who has the most to lose.
- 马赛尔
- 他会杀了他们的
-Marcel.
-No. He'll kill them.
洁妮薇向我证实了
马赛尔被施了个隐身咒
Genevieve assures me that Marcel
has procured a cloaking spell.
唯一会帮助马赛尔的女巫就是黛维娜
The only witch who will aid Marcel
is Davina.
我只需要再收集一点筹码
I just need to get
one last bit of leverage
然后就去拜访她
before I pay her a visit.
筹码来了
And there it is.
你好，约书亚
Hello, Joshua.
黛维娜
Davina.
小约？
Josh?
- 对不起
- 发生什么事了？
-I'm sorry.
-What happened?
约书亚被狼人咬了
KLAUS: Joshua went
and got himself a werewolf bite.
正确地说是混合种咬的
但都一样会要他的命
Well, a hybrid bite, technically
but it will kill him just the same.
- 你为什么要这么做？
- 这都怪你
-Why are you doing this?
-I blame you.
尽管我主动向你表示善意
你还是选择站在马赛尔那边
After my overtures of friendship,
you once again sided with Marcel,
让我不得不对你在乎的人
做一些残忍的事
forcing me to do horrible things
to someone you care about.
我也没那么残忍，黛维娜
我可以治好他
I'm not without mercy, Davina.
I can cure him,
但你必须合作
告诉我马赛尔在哪里
but you have to cooperate
and tell me where to find Marcel.
为什么？好让你也杀了他吗？
Why? So you can kill him too?
马赛尔选择了他的立场
Marcel chose his path.
但让小约为此受罪似乎不太公平
Seems unfair that Josh
should have to suffer for it.
- 黛维娜，拜托…
- 他在码头的一个仓库里
-Davina. Please.
-He's at a warehouse at the docks.
提艾里的住所
Thierry's place.
瞧，这也不是太难，对吧？
You see?
That wasn't so hard, now was it?
那小约怎么办？
What about Josh?
他还能再活一天
Well, he'll live another 24 hours
or so.
我可能还会需要你
约书亚就是最好的筹码
I may need you, and Joshua serves
as wonderful leverage.
下次我再提问的时候
回答得快点
The next time I ask a question,
answer quicker.
谢谢你抽出时间
CAMlLLE: Thank you for your time.
I didn't realize
直到看到我叔叔的遗嘱
我才知道他还有这么个地方
my uncle even had this place
until a read about it in his will.
我的家族守着这个房子几十年了
This building has been in my family
for decades.
在卡崔娜飓风后
你叔叔帮助我们筹款修缮了它
Your uncle helped us raise the funds
to restore it after Katrina.
我注意到他把这个房间留出来了
I figured he'd kept this room
for extra space.
总之，我什么也没问
Anyway, I didn't ask any questions.
你知道，基神父，他是一个好人
You know, Father K,
he was as good as they come.
节哀顺变
Sorry for your loss.
可以让我自己进去吗？
Um.
Do you mind if I go in alone?
（梧桐街456号310室）
宝藏原来在这啊
Here's to buried treasure.
你好啊
Hello.
（给卡蜜）
以利亚那边该有消息了
Elijah should've called by now.
担心也没有用
Worrying isn't going to help.
你应该坐下来，保持冷静
You should sit down,
try to keep calm.
你现在是什么了？
巫师外加禅宗人生导师吗？
What are you now,
magician-slash-Zen life coach?
虽然与我当护士时相比
The treatment of pregnant women
孕妇的治疗方法有了巨大的进步
has advanced remarkably
since I was a nurse,
但我也知道高血压
对你和你的孩子不好
but even I know high blood pressure
is bad for you and your baby.
尤其是你马上就要足月了
especially now
that you're so close to term.
我讨厌这样
我感觉自己很没用
I hate this.
I feel completely useless.
你还不明白吗？
你才是这一切的意义所在
Don't you get it?
You're the point of all this.
克劳斯和以利亚四处奔波
Klaus and Elijah
running all over town,
都是为了你啊
我都有点嫉妒了
it's all for you.
I'm a bit envious.
很好，我真幸运
Great. Lucky me.
- 有什么我能给你的吗？
- 月光戒指怎么样？
-ls there anything I can get you?
-How about a moonlight ring?
到月圆之夜
The spell can't be performed
才能施咒
until the full moon
reaches its apex.
当然，我需要那些石头
它们很快就会送到这里了
And, of course, I need the stones,
which will be here soon enough.
有点信心吧
Have a little faith.
得表扬马赛尔
Accolades to Marcel.
他对你的鼻梁可是费了一番工夫
He did quite a dance
across the bridge of your nose.
他现在在哪？
Where is he now?
哪儿都找不到
Nowhere to be found.
不过他倒是留给我们一个
不错的饯别礼
Although he did leave us
a delightful parting gift.
- 石头呢？
- 不知道
-What about the stones?
-I don't know.
- 放开我，我会帮你们找的
- 乖乖坐着
-Untie me. I'll help you find them.
-Sit still.
只要安全了就会放了你
You'll be freed
as soon as it's safe.
我们应该把重点放在石头上
Our focus should be the stones.
考虑到杰克森也想得到海莉的爱
Considering Jackson is competition
for Hayley's affection,
我想你会同意的
I think you'd agree.
别理我弟弟
Disregard my brother.
过了一千年
Over the course
of the last millennium,
他的才智已有所减弱
his capacity for tact
has somewhat diminished.
这很典型，不是吗？
Oh, that's typical, isn't it?
马赛尔将一间屋子塞满炸药
而我却是没脑子的那个
Marcel fills a room with dynamite
and yet I'm the tactless one.
我认出这些炸药就是攻击河口的那种
I recognize these explosives
from the attack on the bayou.
你能再提醒我一下
Could you remind me again
你为什么觉得马赛尔是无辜的吗？
why you believed
that Marcel was innocent?
提醒我在挖出他的内脏之前问问他
Remind me to ask him
before I pull out his innards.
好吧，在这片区域活动要非常小心
Okay. Exercise extreme caution
in this general area.
有点乱
-(CELL PHONE RlNGS)
-Bit of a mess.
（海莉来电）
真是好时机
Impeccable timing.
- 怎么了？
- 杰克森没事
-What's going on?
-Jackson is fine.
他现在有点抽不开身
晚点回给你好吗？
He's a little tied up right now.
Could we call you back?
- 不太妙啊
- 你是想害死我们吗？
-Oh, that doesn't bode well.
-Are you trying to kill us?
以利亚，告诉我怎么了？
Elijah, tell me what's going on now.
这是为了提艾里
"This is for Thierry."
- 我可以
- 谢天谢地你还活着
-JACK: Oh, I got it.
-Thank God you're alive.
我也很好，多谢关心
I'm fine too.
Thanks for asking.
石头怎么样了？
What about the stones?
我猜是散落在密西西比河的河底了
Scattered across the bed
of the Mississippi, I imagine.
马赛尔不傻
Marcel is no fool.
他知道一支变强大的狼人军队
He knows an empowered
werewolf army
就意味着纽奥良吸血鬼的末日
would mean the end of vampires
in New Orleans.
爆炸就是他表示要阻止这事的方式
The explosion is his way of saying
he means to prevent that,
对他有利
for all the good it'll do him.
对他真是太有利了，不是吗？
Well, it did him pretty damn well,
didn't it?
这是我的错，我会想办法弥补
This is my fault.
I will find a way to fix it.
不，杰克，你受伤了
而且没人责怪你
No, Jack. You're hurt,
and no one is blaming you.
我就责怪你
I'm blaming you.
那些石头难以取代
Those stones
will be hard to replace.
幸运的是，我总是有备用计划
Fortunately, I always have
a backup plan.
你不是指她吧，她可是大坏蛋
You can't seriously mean her.
She's a gangster.
我见识过她
I see her more as a means
在很短时间里取得稀有物品
to procuring rare items
at short notice.
欢迎，科雷亚女士
我看到你带了人来
Greetings, Ms. Correa.
I see you've brought company.
这些是我的兄弟
These are my brothers.
我总是会带着他们做愉快的生意
I always include them
in delicate business matters.
各位，这就是米卡森先生
Fellas, meet Mr. Mikaelson.
叫我克劳斯就行
我朋友们都这么叫我
Please, call me Klaus.
All my friends do.
我不知道我们算不算是朋友
I don't know if I'd call us friends.
但如果你和马赛尔打算拚个你死我活
But if you and Marcel are planning
on having a little throw down,
我希望我的家人
I'd prefer my family
能够和必胜者站在同一边
to be on the same side
as the inevitable victor.
你带来了我要的东西
Then you have what I asked for.
这么短时间建立一支军队来不及
但这也是开端了
Not enough for an army at
such short notice, but it's a start.
奇怪，我并不知道她很了解我们的计划
Strange, I wasn't aware
that she was familiar with our plan.
和我谈生意的条件就是我要知悉全局
FRANCESCA: My price
for doing business is full disclosure.
你弟弟连守要求了
Your brother complied.
人类决策群想从这事里得到什么好处？
And what does the human faction
expect to benefit from all this?
我只想重申对统治阶层的忠诚
I only wanna solidify our allegiance
to the ruling class.
有利生意
It's good for business.
要是大家都像你这么通情达理就好了
If only everyone shared
your capacity for reason.
可惜他们没有
Sadly, they don't.
马赛尔现在复仇心极重
Marcel is being
especially vindictive.
我担心他会因为我和你见面
I'm worried he might
come after me or my family
而对付我或是我的家人
just for meeting with you.
如果我们能联合起来才对我们最有利
It might be in our best interests
if we combine our efforts.
那就这样吧
So be it.
越多人保护宅邸越好
The more bodies we have
to defend the compound, the better.
我们开始吧
Let's get started, shall we?
- 好了
- 谢谢
-There.
-Thank you.
别谢我，是以利亚救了你
Don't thank me. It was Elijah
who vamped your ass to safety.
是啊
他似乎真的很在乎你
Yeah. Well, he really seems
to care about you.
这很复杂
It's complicated.
我想这是本年度最佳保守陈述
I think that's the
understatement of the year.
我该走了
在月亮升起前
Look. I gotta go,
get back to the bayou
回到河口
before the moon rises, so....
杰克森，这会是最后一次
Jackson, this will be the last time.
今晚过后，你就再也不用变身了
After tonight,
you'll never have to turn again.
没有痛苦，不用躲在河口，我保证
No more pain, no more hiding
in the bayou, I promise.
你知道，克劳斯并不是真心要这么做
You know, Klaus isn't doing this
out of the kindness of his heart.
他是为了你，海莉
He's doing it for you, Hayley.
是你改变了我们的一切
You're the one who's gonna change
everything for us.
看来我又欠你一次了
Seems I owe you yet again.
我明白他冒着生命危险救他的朋友
I understand he risked his life
to save his friend.
- 他是个好人
- 是的
-He's a good man.
-Yes, he is.
以利亚，我有事要告诉你
Elijah, there is something
that I need to tell you.
我的家人想让我…
My family wanted me....
我和杰克森有婚约在先
I was supposed to be
betrothed to Jackson.
我本来想早点告诉你
我只是不知道该如何开口
I wanted to tell you sooner.
I just didn't know how.
这是个荒唐的习俗
It's this insane custom--
不，你不需要解释什么
No.
You don't need to explain anything.
我明白需要为家人做出牺牲
I understand the need
to make sacrifices for one's family.
别这样，以利亚
Oh, come on, Elijah.
在你无尽的生命里
你就不能有一次不这么高尚吗？
For once in your immortal life,
can you just not be so noble?
那你希望我怎么做？
What would you have me do?
我只是告诉你因为一些
I just told you that I'm betrothed
我不认识的人订下的规矩
according to some
backwater arrangement
我有了婚约
by people that I never knew.
告诉我你觉得这样的订婚很愚蠢
Tell me that you think
betrothals are stupid.
告诉我我有选择
Tell me that I have a choice.
你永远都有选择
You will always have a choice.
我相信你已经准备好了
I trust you are ready.
最后一样材料是很私人的
The last ingredient is personal.
这个咒语的目的是控制变身
As this spell is designed
to control transformation,
我需要不在月圆时变身的狼人的血
I need the blood of a werewolf
who doesn't turn on a full moon.
我的第一人选是海莉，因为她怀孕了
My first thought was Hayley
because of the pregnancy--
不可能
Out of the question.
我宁愿我未出生孩子的母亲
I'd just as soon limit
the mother of my unborn child
不要受到你巫术的副作用影响
to the side effects
of your witchery.
我是半狼人，我控制住了我的狼形
I am half wolf.
I control my form.
用我的血
Use my blood.
如果你未能完成你的交易
If you fail to uphold
your end of the deal,
那你的后果将会不堪设想
the consequences for you
will be apocalyptic.
你说了最浪漫的事
You say the most romantic things.
感谢你们都来了，已经有一段时间了
I appreciate you all coming.
It's been a while.
到目前为止，你们听说了现在的情况
By now,
you've heard what's going on.
克劳斯找到了让狼人
对我们随时有威胁的办法
Klaus found a way to make
werewolves lethal to us 24/7.
码头的爆炸是我
The fireworks at the docks,
that was me
试图破坏他的计划
trying to spoil his plan.
但他的计划还是继续实行了
He's moving forward anyway.
他有巫女，有咒语
He's got as witch, he's got a spell,
如果他成功了
and if he pulls this off,
一夜之间
我们就会从猎人变成猎物
in one night,
we go from hunter to prey.
我知道你们有人在想
Now I know
what some of you all are thinking.
我们以前反抗过克劳斯，但失败了
We stood against Klaus before,
and we failed.
那是我的问题，我失败了
Uh-uh. That's on me. I failed.
我放弃了攻击
因为我以为那是救大家的唯一办法
I called off the attack because l
thought it the only way to save lives.
但毫无疑问
But make no mistake.
如果我们现在不反抗他
If we don't stand against him now,
我们的生命一样不值钱
our lives aren't worth a damn
anyway!
智者说
Wise man said,
“知己知彼
if you know yourself
and know your enemy,
百战不殆
then you don't need to fear
the outcome of battle.
我了解我自己，了解我的朋友
I know myself.
I know my friends.
也了解我的敌人
And I know my enemy.
我知道他的优势，知道他的得意
I know his strengths,
I know his pride.
我对他房子的每一个角落都了如指掌
And I know his house,
every nook and cranny.
我们今晚就去
We're gonna go there tonight,
同时从各个角度下手，要快狠准
hard and fast,
all at once, from every angle.
杀了他们的女巫
We kill their witch,
毁了她的魔法书，然后离开
destroy her spell book,
and get the hell out.
至于克劳斯，他会来追杀我
And as for Klaus,
he'll be coming for me.
那正是我想要的
我会引开他
And that's exactly what I want.
I'll lead him away.
你们其他人要通过以利亚
I just need the rest of you
to get past Elijah
做该做的事情
and do what needs to be done.
这就是计划
So that's the plan.
我现在就要知道，谁支持我？
I need to know right now!
Who's with me?
我的人说马赛尔要行动了
还带着他的朋友
My people say Marcel is on the move
and he's bringing friends.
把海莉带到安全的地方
Get Hayley to safety.
- 跟我走
- 不
-Come with me.
-No.
得有人看着她
Someone needs to watch her.
你应该帮克劳斯
You should help Klaus.
我的兄弟们和他们的随从
对付不了吸血鬼军队
My brothers and their security
won't be much against a vampires.
我留下来陪海莉
I'll stay with Hayley.
去吧，以利亚
Go, Elijah.
不要退缩
And don't hold back.
我以为这群人会学到教训
I thought this lot
would've learned their lesson.
他们没那么聪明
Well, they're not exactly renowned
for their genius.
那么这个杂耍团的领导者是谁？
So where's the ringleader
of this circus?
太害怕而不敢露面吗？
Too afraid to show his face?
我在这里
I'm here.
给你们最后一次机会
And I'm gonna offer you
one last chance.
收拾好东西
滚出我的城市
To pack your stuff
and get the hell out of my town.
你又一次让你的人匆匆送死了
You'll allow your men
to rush to their deaths again?
看看四周吧
法语区所有吸血鬼都来了
Look around. Every vampire
in the Quarter is coming out.
他们想要收回城市
这次绝不投降
They want their city back,
no surrender this time.
- 你得把我们都杀了
- 好吧
-You're gonna have to kill us all.
-Okay.
我想那就先从你开始吧
I think I'll start with you.
好啊，来抓我吧
Fine. Come get me.
- 如果你不杀他，我会的
- 他是我的
-lf you don't kill him, I will.
-He's mine.
不会太久
This won't take long.
先生们
Gentlemen.
开始吧
Shall we?
不错
但还是不够好
Not bad, but not nearly good enough.
你太可悲了
How pathetic you've become.
炸药，马赛勒斯，是吗？
Explosives, Marcellus, really?
我该知道河口的爆炸就是你指使的
I should've know it was you who
detonated those bombs in the bayou.
码头，是我
The docks, that was me.
炸药是佛朗西丝卡给的
I got the detonators from Francesca.
你怎么不问问她河口爆炸的事呢？
Why don't you ask her
about the bayou bombing?
谎言，顾左右而言他
Lies and distractions.
我从没对付过海莉
I never went after Hayley.
我不是禽兽，克劳斯
I'm not a monster, Klaus.
我不是你
I'm not you.
（盖布里尔科雷亚
出生证明窜改？)
（葛雷拉狼人还在法语区吗？
我的家族在纽奥良生活很久了
My family has been in New Orleans
for a long time.
侧面攻击，立刻拿下他
Flank him. Take him down now!
科雷亚女士，我们该走了
Miss Correa, we need to go.
- 你的兄弟们已经从后面走了
- 还不行
Your brother's already
heading out the back.
Not yet.
（卡蜜来电）
石头成功了，我已经完成了我的任务
The stones are finished.
I've done my part.
- 现在就看你了
- 我把它们送去河口
-Now it's up to you.
-I'll get them to the bayou.
事实上，她是对我说的
Actually, she was talking to me.
这是怎么回事？
What the hell is this?
私下交易
Call it a side deal.
重点是，石头归我了
Point is, I'm taking the stones.
你疯了吗？
Are you out of your mind?
你觉得人类能对抗克劳斯？
You think humans
can go up against Klaus?
不，我不这么认为
No, I don't.
但我不是人类
But I'm not human.
我和你一样，海莉
I'm like you, Hayley.
现在我要夺回我的城市
Now I'm gonna take back my town.
一样才怪
Like hell, you are.
别这么阴沉，洁妮薇
我们都得到了各自想要的
Don't look so dour, Genevieve.
We both got what we wanted.
马赛勒斯
KLAUS: Marcellus.
你的名字真配你
“小战士”
How well your name fits you,
"little warrior."
最后却无足轻重
Though ultimately,
one of no consequence.
我的名字是马赛尔
My name is Marcel.
你的反抗没完了是吗？
Is there no end to your defiance?
你召唤了麦可
让蕾贝卡与我为敌
You summoned Mikael,
turned Rebekah against me,
试图把我埋在你的花园里
tried to bury me in your garden,
但你总是失败
and yet you always fail.
还能做什么呢？
只能让你从痛苦中解脱了
What is there left to do
but put you out of your misery?
海莉，我已经打了六次电话
回我电话
Hayley, I've called six times.
Call me back.
你说你想知道我是否知道
佛朗西丝卡科雷亚的事
You said you wanted to know
if I learned anything
about Francesca Correa.
她的家人是狼人的后裔
Her family is descended
from a werewolf bloodline.
我们两代人都活在谎言里
We've spent two generations
living a lie,
现在我们的时代…
and now our time...
我们的时代来临了
our time has come.
你们知道怎么做
You know what do to.
结束了吗？
Are we done?
干得漂亮
Nice job.
帮我省了亲自杀死这些吸血鬼的麻烦
Saved me the trouble of killing
all these vampires myself.
快跑
Run!
能杀多少杀多少
Kill as many of them as you can.
抱歉，老兄，但我有点饿了
I'm sorry, mate.
But I'm a bit famished.
你看起来很糟糕呢
You look awful.
我为什么还没治愈好？
你对我做了什么？
Why aren't I healing?
What have you done to me?
是你要我施咒的
You were the one
who wanted me to cast the spell.
所以我就做了你的石头
So I made your stones,
把它们的力量和你的血液连在一起
by linking their power
to your blood.
现在每次月圆，只要有狼人
使用它们的力量不变身
Each full moon whenever a werewolf
uses their power to keep from turning,
他们就会吸取你的力量
they will be drawing
from your strength
给你造成痛苦
and causing you pain.
我给你那么多，你却背叛我？
After all I offered you,
you will betray me?
看着我的眼睛，尼克
Look me in the eyes, Nik.
你有没有打算要给我你母亲的魔法书？
Were you ever planning to give me
your mother's grimoire?
你在乎过我吗，哪怕是一瞬间？
Did you care about me
even for a moment?
我想你永远不会知道了
I suppose you'll never know.
佛朗西丝卡遵守了交易
Francesca kept her end of the deal.
毕竟，盗亦有道
There is, after all,
honor among thieves.
即使他们是狼人
Even if they are werewolves.
至于你，最讽刺的是
And as for you, the great irony is,
想要得到这座城市，你却失去了一切
in wanting to take the city,
you've lost everything.
你的妹妹蕾贝卡
你的养子马赛尔
Your sister, Rebekah,
your adopted son, Marcel.
现在就连你的孩子和她的母亲都会受苦
And now even your child
and her mother will suffer,
都是因为你的贪婪
all because of your greed.
我会杀了你
I will kill you.
就你这副弱鸡样？
As weak as you are?
深表怀疑
Doubtful.
小约，拜托，喝下这个
Josh, please drink this.
- 天啊
- 求求你撑住
-Oh, man.
-Just hang on, please.
不！
No!
当然你并不惊讶
Surely, you're not surprised.
内心深处，你知道尼克劳斯
会任由约书亚死去
Deep down, you knew Niklaus
would leave Joshua to die.
你为什么还在这里？
Why are you still here?
我没多少时间了
不过，你的朋友也是
I haven't much time left.
But then, neither does your friend.
我能治好他，我会想到办法的
I can heal him. I'll find a way.
即使你可以
隔多久又会再次发生呢？
Even if you could,
how long till it happens again?
只要尼克劳斯留在纽奥良
As long as Niklaus
remains in New Orleans,
你和你所爱的人将继续遭受他的折磨
you and your loved ones
will continue to suffer his torment.
这世上只有我
I am the only man in history
能够把他赶走
带给他恐惧和痛苦
who's been able to drive him off,
to bring him fear and pain.
如果你朋友需要克劳斯的血活下来
If your friend
needs Klaus' blood to survive,
我了解如何公平分配
I've been known to spill
a fair share of it.
你会帮我救小约吗？
You'll help me save Josh?
我的确有私人原因
希望尼克劳斯受到折磨
I do have personal reasons
for wanting Niklaus to suffer.
不过…
是的
But...yes.
我非常想帮你
I'd like nothing more
than to help you.
我只要让你死而复生
And all I have to do
is raise you from the dead.
一个治愈你朋友，并且一生
A small price to pay
to cure your friend
摆脱怪物阴影的小小代价
and live a life free of a monster.
想一想，黛维娜
Think, Davina.
依然有可以杀死克劳斯的武器
There still exists a weapon
that can kill Klaus.
让唯一一个有能力使用它的人活过来
Bring back the one being
who has the strength to use it.
你在跟谁说话？
Who were you talking to?
不重要，我要治好你
Doesn't matter. I'm gonna fix you.
完成了
It's done.
交易必须遵守
A deal is a deal.
你说爆炸威力很小
You said the bombing
was gonna be minor.
不会造成死伤
No casualties.
我只不过想要让新月族
团结起来对抗吸血鬼
All I wanted to do was rally
the Crescents against the vampires.
事情不正好就是这样吗？
And isn't that exactly what happened?
有人死了
People died.
我的族人，我的狼群
My people, my pack!
你的狼群？
Your pack?
真有意思
That's funny.
因为在我看来他们已经
准备好跟随海莉了
Because it looked to me
they were ready to follow Hayley.
但现在，多亏了我
But now, thanks to me,
我们掌握了唯一能够激发新月族
we have control of the very thing
that will inspire loyalty
和葛雷拉家族忠心的东西
from both the Crescents
and the Guerreras.
让我们的人变得更加强大的方法
The means to make our people
even more powerful.
我唯一要交换掉的东西
The only thing I had to trade away
则是一个会带给我们威胁的人
was the one person
who could've challenged us.
可怜的海莉，真是可惜了
Poor Hayley. It is a shame.
女巫极力讨价还价
The witches drive a hard bargain.
但每一场革命都要有牺牲
But every revolution
requires sacrifice.
这座城市将再次属于狼人
This city will belong
to the wolves again.
我们唯一要做的…
就是夺回它
All we have to do...
is take it.
不…
No. No, no, no.
不
No.
不，不！
No, no, no!
马赛尔
Marcel.
马赛尔，抱歉
Marcel, I'm sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
天啊，马赛尔
Oh, my God, Marcel.
我已经试着找人来了，任何人
I've been trying to find someone,
anyone.
- 发生了什么事？
- 你得离开这里
-What's happening?
-You need to get out of here.
我的人被狼人咬了
My guys have been bitten by wolves.
他们会生病，然后嗜血
They'll get sick
and then bloodcrazy.
我们得找到克劳斯，他的血能治愈你们
We need to find Klaus.
His blood can heal you.
马赛尔，她在哪？
ELlJAH: Marcel! Where is she?
- 海莉在哪？
- 海莉不在他手上，拜托
-Where's Hayley?
-He doesn't have her.
我知道你不相信他
但你知道我不会说谎
Please, I know you don't trust him,
but you know I wouldn't lie.
海莉不在他手上
He doesn't have her.
有人抓走了她
Someone does.
我弟弟呢？
Where's my brother?
我把他留在街上了
I left him in the street.
他本来要杀了我
He was gonna kill me,
然后被女巫的咒语攻击了
and then he got jacked up
by some witch's spell.
洁妮薇
Genevieve.
不
No.
- 把她放在地板上
- 我们应该把她带去墓地
Get her down on the floor.
We should take her
to the City of the Dead.
没时间了，孩子马上就要出生了
We won't make it.
The baby is coming now.
- 不，太早了
- 显然不早
-No. It's too soon.
-Apparently not.
计划是献祭准备好时才让她开始
The plan was to induce her
when the sacrifice was ready.
我不得不制服她
外伤导致胎盘早剥
I had to subdue her, and the trauma
caused a placental abruption.
孩子马上就要出生，我们得做好调整
So the baby is coming,
and we'll just have to adapt.
- 放我走！
- 你要冷静，海莉
-Let me go!
-You need to be calm, Hayley.
你为什么要这样对我？
Why are you doing this to me?
为了重生，我们必须献祭
To be reborn, we must sacrifice.
那是什么意思？你这神经病小贱人
What the hell does that mean,
you psychotic little bitch?
祖先们要求用祭品来换取力量
The ancestors demand an offering
in exchange for power.
而你的孩子将会是最好的祭品
And your child
will be a fine offering.
不，不要
No. No!
你们不能拿走我的孩子，我会杀了你们
You will not take my baby.
I will kill all of you.
不，你不会
克劳斯和以利亚也不行
No, you won't.
And neither will Klaus or Elijah.
你孩子出生后
我们会将她献祭给我们的祖先
When your baby is born,
we will offer it up
to those who came before us.
对不起，海莉
但只能这样了
I'm sorry, Hayley.
But this is the way it had to be.
不，不要！
No! No!
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）